{
  "questions": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "Year has how many months",
      "answers": [ "12", "7", "366" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "Leap Year has how many days",
      "answers": [ "12", "7", "366" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "question": "Week has how many days",
      "answers": [ "12", "7", "366" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "Day has how many hours",
      "answers": [ "12", "24", "366" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "A month can have how many days",
      "answers": [ "28, 29", "30, 31", "both" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "February has how many days",
      "answers": [ "28, 29", "30, 31", "29, 30" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "February has how many days in leap year",
      "answers": [ "29", "28", "both" ], "correct_answer": 1
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "What is written for time in morning",
      "answers": [ "EM", "PM", "AM" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "What is written for time in after noon",
      "answers": [ "EM", "PM", "AM" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "What is written for time in evening",
      "answers": [ "EM", "PM", "AM" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 11,
      "question": "2 hours before 11:15",
      "answers": [ "8:15", "10:15", "09:15" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 12,
      "question": "3 hours after 1:20",
      "answers": [ "3:20", "4:20", "5:20" ], "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "number": 13,
      "question": "2 hours after 11 AM",
      "answers": [ "1 AM", "12 PM", "1 PM" ], "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "number": 14,
      "question": "3 hours before 2 PM",
      "answers": [ "11 PM", "11 AM", "12 PM" ], "correct_answer": 2
    }
  ]
}

